What beautiful pictures! What is it?
好美的照片  这是什么
Oh, that is Big Ben.
哦 那是大本钟
Long ago, the queen of England knew that many clocks had different time.
很久以前  英国女王发现各个钟的时间不一样
People were either early or late.
人们总是早了或是晚了
She had it built so that everyone would have the same time.
她就命人造了这个大钟  这样所有人的时间就一样了
Now it is a symbol of England.
现在它是英国的象征
Oh! What about the building that looks like a huge sailing boat?
哦  这个像是一艘巨大帆船的建筑物是什么
That is a good description.
你这个比喻太形象了
It's the Opera House in Sydney, Australia.
这是澳大利亚的悉尼歌剧院
It's the pride of Australians.
它是澳大利亚的骄傲
Do you know the picture below it?
你知道下面这张是什么吗
That's the Statue of Liberty!
那是 自由女神像
It was designed by Gustave Eiffel as a gift from France to the USA.
它由古斯塔夫·埃菲尔设计  法国把它作为礼物送给了美国
It stands in New York Harbor.
它屹立在纽约港
That's right,
是的
but do you know that Eiffel designed not only the Statue of Liberty
但是你知道吗  埃菲尔不仅设计了自由女神像
but also the Eiffel Tower?
还设计了埃菲尔铁塔
He was a great leader in the arts.
他曾是伟大的艺术先驱
Is this Eiffel Tower?
这是埃菲尔铁塔吗
Yes, it was built for the International Exhibition of Paris in 1889.
是的  它是因为1889年的巴黎国际展览会而建的
I really hope I can visit some of these places some day.
我好希望某一天能去这些地方看看